Everyone has an angel.
A guardian who watches over us.
We can't know what form they'll take.
One day, old man.
Next day, little girl.
But don't let appearances fool you.
They can be as fierce as any dragon.
Yet they're not here to fight our battles...
...but to whisper from our heart...
...reminding that it's us.
It's every one of us who holds
the power over the worlds we create.
No!
No.
We can deny our angels exist...
...convince ourselves they can't be real.
But they show up anyway.
At strange places.
And at strange times.
They can speak through any character
we can imagine.
They'll shout through demons
if they have to...
...daring us...
...challenging us to fight.
Female. Age 20.
- You're the father?
- Stepfather.
That's right. We talked on the phone.
Okay, come with me.
We're gonna take her into the theater.
Dr. Gorski's gonna want to take a look
at her. She likes to see all the new girls.
Don't worry, Dad.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I've got everything under control
around here.
Okay? Come on. Follow me.
So this is what we call the theater.
Liar!
Oh, girls. Yes, go, go.
Hey. Come here.
Girls. Behave.
Break it up. Break it up.
Will you stop them?
Lynn.
Amy.
Sit down.
Sit.
Anyway.
So the girls use this place to be social.
Dr. Gorski, she uses it to help them
deal with their issues.
Polish therapy.
It's quite a show, watching them act out
who touched them or beat them.
Dr. Gorski seems to think it helps.
I'm not so sure.
But whether it does or doesn't
won't matter much to you.
Once we take care of
a little bit of business...
...there won't be any of that for this one.
Good.
She'll be in paradise,
if you know what I mean.
And all of your troubles will be over.
Now, I know we said 1400
on the phone...
I'm taking a really big risk here...
...so it's gonna have to be 2 grand even.
What the hell are you talking about?
We had a deal.
Listen, Father,
I'm not gonna tell you what to do.
Clearly you're a man that can take
care of himself.
I don't know what you did to this girl.
And, frankly, I don't wanna know.
What are you gonna tell the detectives
when they come around?
They're gonna love her side of the story.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I'm going to start your music.
You are safe.
It's all safe.
Now relax.
And just let go.
Now, here's the other thing:
I don't have a doctor on staff
who does lobotomies.
- What?
- But...
...there happens to be one scheduled
to come in in five days.
So I'll just forge her signature.
I've done it a dozen times.
It's like we talk about.
You control this world.
I told the police
she lost her mind when her mother died.
The truth is a little more complicated.
Let the pain go.
Let the hurt go.
Let the guilt go.
What you're imagining right now...
...that world you control?
That place can be as real as any pain.
I don't want her to remember a thing.
Don't worry, she won't even remember
her name when I'm done with her.
Stop.
Get that thing away from me.
Get it away from me.
Where is my mind?
And shut off that damn music.
Undo these straps.
Don't forget my ankles.
Hurry.
Is there a problem, Sweet Pea?
This is a joke, right?
Don't you get the point of this?
It's to turn people on.
I get the sexy little schoolgirl.
I even get the helpless mental patient,
right? That can be hot.
But what is this?
Lobotomized vegetable?
How about something a little more
commercial, for God's sakes?
Sweet Pea,
could you come here, please?
You gotta help me.
I'm the star of the show, remember?
I'll figure something out.
All right, ladies. Wrap it up.
Sweet Pea, I want you
to meet somebody. This...
Don't tell me.
The priest brought you here from the
orphanage to lose your virginity, right?
Oh, let me rephrase that.
To sell it.
Heh, heh, heh. Yeah, that's right.
How original.
The High Roller is coming for her
in five days.
He's gonna, you know,
just do a little flower picking.
And he's gonna pay
a lot of money for that.
Mm. Luck you.
Can you do me a favor, honey?
Can you show this little baby doll around,
give her a tour of the establishment?
Blue, you saw the show, okay?
I don't have the time.
Let my sister take her.
Rocket.
Show her around, will you, sis?
All right, come on. Let's go.
Don't worry, I don't bite very hard.
Goodbye, my dear.
- Jesus!
- Oh...
You'll get what you deserve
when the High Roller comes!
Calm down.
I will not calm down.
- You see what she did? I hope you rot!
- I did. I'm sorry.
This way.
You're gonna be okay.
It just takes a little while to get used to.
So how'd you become an orphan?
Oh, I get it. It's complicated, right?
Well, we all have our stories in here.
Mine's...
...complicated.
These are the rooms
where we take the clients.
There's fresh towels
in all the bathrooms and...
Turn that on.
Blue owns the club.
And we, my dear, heh...
...are the main attractions. Ta-da.
The club's a front for his business.
Guns, gambling, medications,
special favors.
He brings in his clients,
and we gotta make them feel, you know...
...special.
New girl.
This is our backstage.
It's just for us, so don't bring any clients
back here, okay? Or Blue's gonna get pissed.
Uh, cleaning closet.
You'll find all the
mops, brooms, disinfectants.
New girls get cleaning duties.
I don't make the rules.
And if you don't do what you're told,
Blue locks us in here...
...until we become
a bit more cooperative.
Don't worry.
It's not gonna happen to you.
This is the kitchen.
We all work in here.
Time for rehearsal.
She looked nice.
She looked stuck-up to me.
No. She's scared.
I feel sorry for her.
Amber, you feel sorry for everyone.
Do you remember when you first got here?
Nobody felt sorry for you.
Well, don't get too attached to her, okay?
Blue's saving her for the High Roller.
She's no virgin.
Babydoll, that's Amber, Blondie,
and you've met my sister, Sweet Pea.
- Watch yourself.
- Come on, just give her a break.
Yeah, she hasn't done anything
to you guys.
You best friends now?
Will you just let me finish my tour,
please?
Thank you.
Everybody gets a dance, a routine.
We practice, practice, practice,
and the men come and watch us perform.
And if they like what they see...
Well, you'll see tonight.
Good evening, gentlemen.
We've got a great night
in store for you.
I see a lot of new faces out there.
As well as some familiar ones.
So I'm not gonna yammer on too long.
I want you all to sit back,
enjoy the service...
...the scenery.
But most of all, enjoy the show.
Hit it.
Ooh. All right.
It ain't no big thing
To wait for the bell to ring
The toll of the bell
Aggravated, spare for days
I troll downtown
The red light place
Jump up, bubble up
What's in store
Love is the drug
And I need to score
Showing out, showing out,
Hit and run
Boy meets girl
Well, the beat goes on
Stitched up tight
I can't shake free
Because love is the drug for me
Oh
Love is the drug
Late that night I park my car
Stake my place in the singles bar
Face to face,
Toe to toe
Heart to heart as we hit the floor
Lumber up, limbo down
The locked embrace, the stumble round
I say go
And I say yes
Dim the lights, you can guess the rest
Oh
Love is the drug
Love is
Love is the drug for me
Oh, catch that buzz
Because love is the drug
I'm thinking of
Oh
Can't you see
Love is the drug
Got a hook in me
Oh, catch that buzz
Because love is the drug that I'm thinking of
Oh, can't you see
Love is the drug for me
Ain't no big thing
Yeah, no big thing
Whoo!
Can't you see
Love is the drug for me
Oh
Love is the drug
Love is, love is
Drug, drug. The drug is love.
Give me that.
Somebody! Help me!
Shh.
Let her go, pig.
I didn't mean nothing.
Just having a little fun.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Let's just go.
We don't wanna be late.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
arms, six, seven, eight. Stop.
Stop.
Where are you right now?
Are you with us or not?
Sweet Pea, take break.
Yeah.
Babydoll.
Come over here.
Come, come.
Let me look at you.
Hm.
You seem fit enough.
I'm going to play you some music, okay?
I want you to just relax. Feel the music.
Open your heart to it. Let it in.
And when you are ready...
...I want you to dance.
If you do not dance,
you have no purpose.
And we don't keep things here
that have no purpose.
You see, your fight for survival
starts right now.
You don't want to be judged?
You won't be.
You don't think you're strong enough?
You are.
You're afraid. Don't be.
You have all the weapons you need.
Now fight.
Again.
Stand up
You've got to manage
Hello?
- Excuse me, could you help me? I'm...
Shoes.
I'm sorry?
Your shoes.
You're tracking snow everywhere.
Oh, I'm sorry. Should I take them off?
That time has passed.
What can I do for you?
Nothing. I just...
Let me ask it another way:
What are you looking for?
A way out, I guess.
You guess?
No, I...
I know.
I need to get out of here.
Freedom.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
I'm going to help you to be free.
What do I have to do?
These are your weapons.
When you take them,
you begin your journey.
Your journey to freedom.
You will need five items for this journey.
The first is a map.
Then fire, a knife and a key.
You said five things.
The fifth thing is a mystery.
It is the reason. It is the goal.
It will be a deep sacrifice
and a perfect victory.
Only you can find it.
And if you do...
...it will set you free.
Oh, and one more thing:
Defend yourself.
What was that?
Seriously, you're gonna have to
teach me how to dance like that.
That was crazy.
That was so amazing. I'm, like, shaking.
I've never seen Madame Gorski
clap like that before.
Well, get over it.
It's nearly lights out.
She's not easily impressed.
She wasn't impressed.
All that gyrating and moaning.
The dance should be
more than just titillation.
Mine's personal. It says who I am.
What the heck does yours say?
It says I'm gonna escape from here.
That I'm gonna be free.
Well, send me a postcard from paradise.
Are you really gonna try to escape?
Yeah. Before the High Roller comes.
- Can I come?
- Me too.
- Yeah, of course.
- You're not going anywhere, Rocket.
I'm gonna do what I wanna do.
No one's ever escaped from here.
You know that.
Yeah. You know, the last three girls
that tried died.
And the same thing'll happen
to the next fool.
Look, why don't you just
listen to my plan?
Don't wanna hear your plan, okay?
None of us do.
Now, let's get ready, girls.
Rehearsal in 15 minutes.
We're not helping Baby.
- Am I clear?
- What if it's a good plan?
Then she can go through with it.
I'm not letting you get hurt.
- I kept us safe through a lot of shit.
- I know you have.
I'm not gonna get hurt.
I just can't be here anymore.
And if it is a good plan,
we're both going.
No, we're not.
You're on your own.
- Well, I've been on my own before.
Heh.
Sure you have.
Look where that got us.
Baby saved me from the Cook
the other day.
What?
I was working in the kitchen
and he comes in behind me.
And he pushes me down
and he gets on top of me...
...and I can't even move.
And there she was, just like that.
She had a knife to his throat.
She saved me.
The High Roller comes for me
in three days.
But I'm getting out of here
before he does.
So if you guys wanna come with me,
this is how I plan to do it.
Well?
Okay.
If we can collect all four of these items,
we can be free.
Okay.
- How do we use them?
- Wait up.
First things first.
How do you plan on
getting these things?
Well, whoever has the item we need,
we get them to watch me dance.
While we run around
and pick their pockets?
- Yeah, that's right.
- But we'd be taking all the risk.
We'd be doing the work
while you prance around with an alibi.
No. As long as I'm dancing,
they won't even know you're there.
Okay, so the first thing we need
is a map...
...to figure out where all the exits are,
where the guards are located.
Blue has that in his office.
It's behind his desk.
Right. Good.
Second thing we need
is something to start a fire with...
...as a distraction for when we escape.
Plus, the fire should disable
all the checkpoints.
And the third thing is a knife...
...in case we run into trouble.
The Cook.
- We can do it.
- Okay.
And the last thing's a key.
Blue wears a key around his neck.
What door does it open?
It's for all of them, I think.
It's a master key.
This plan is crazy.
There's armed guards everywhere, okay?
And if Blue finds out, we're dead.
It's not gonna be, "Oh, sorry, Blue,
we won't do it again. " We'll be dead.
We're already dead.
- I'm in.
- So am I.
Me too.
All right.
But I'm only doing this because you
guys'd get caught without me, okay?
And if it gets too hairy...
...if I say it's over...
...we stop.
Okay.
I'll get the map.
I went for a walk down the railroad track.
Next thing you know, some...
- What do you want?
- She's dancing.
Who is dancing?
Your baby doll.
One pill makes you larger
And one pill makes you small
Baby.
He's coming.
He's gonna start the briefing.
All right, here's the drill:
The Germans are preparing a report
for the kaiser. It's a map...
...that shows troop locations
and trench layouts.
Their field commander's
sending the map via courier...
...back to Germany
on a zeppelin today.
How do we intercept it?
You're gonna cross no man's land,
enter the enemy trenches...
...and take the map from
the field commander's bunker...
...before the courier
can reach the zeppelin.
Sounds like fun.
Oh, and I've arranged something special
for Amber.
Give you some cover.
Get you out of there when you're done.
Let's go.
What do you think?
I like it.
German doctors and engineers...
...have worked out how to return
their fallen to the front lines.
They're using steam power and clockworks
to keep them moving.
So don't feel bad about killing them.
They're already dead.
Remember, ladies:
If you don't stand for something...
...you'll fall for anything.
Oh, and one last thing:
Try and work together.
Son of a...
Come on, guys. The bunker's this way.
- Cover!
- Rocket!
Sweet Pea! Help!
Unh. Sweet Pea!
Rocket.
Are you okay?
It's right here.
Rocket. That's enough.
OFFICER:
Wow.
- Very good.
- Hm.
- Nice work.
- Thanks.
Very good.
Okay, this gives me an idea.
What about a private dance
for the Mayor.
What?
Nothing touchy-feely, just something
to get him wound up.
Get him ready to spend some money.
All she has to do
is do what she did just now.
That is out of the question.
She is not ready. It is too raw.
Did you just say she's not ready?
She doesn't have a costume.
There is no set.
Honey, she doesn't need that bullshit.
She's perfect.
Perhaps. But that is not for you to decide,
that is for me to decide.
Oh.
It's my show, and I say she's not ready.
Clearly, I've offended you,
and I apologize.
Thank you.
Here's the thing:
This show might be yours...
...but the girls and you...
...are mine.
Right?
You're mine.
And if you need a stronger reminder of that,
you let me know, okay?
That won't be necessary.
So with or without your blessing,
she's gonna be on that stage tomorrow?
- I'll see what I can do.
- Attagirl.
- Mm-hm.
- All right.
You look fantastic, by the way.
Big show, girls.
Thank you.
- For what?
- The Cook.
- It was nothing.
- Shut up.
No one takes a risk for anyone in here.
So thank you.
You're welcome.
You got family?
No.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot, you're an orphan.
I ran away from mine.
I thought I was pretty smart
at the time, but...
Sweet Pea followed.
Which is crazy, because she never even
had a real problem with Mom and Dad.
She just cares about you a lot.
Have you just ever wanted
to just take something back?
You know, something you said.
Something you did.
All the time.
Amber?
The Mayor comes tonight.
I've never seen him without
a big stogie in his mouth.
Ugh. I hate those cigars.
I can never get that stink out of my hair.
- What?
- It's you.
- You have to get his lighter.
- I'm not doing that.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
Come on, be reasonable.
There's got to be another way,
or someone else who can do it.
He's your client.
Yeah, but what if I screw it up?
You can do this.
Well, he keeps it here, you know.
In his breast pocket.
So then you do the good old
kiss-the-neck...
...rub-his-chest...
...reach in...
...and bam...
...you're gold.
Yeah.
Kiss the neck.
- He'll like that.
- Heh, heh.
Don't part with your illusions.
When they are gone, you may still exist,
but you will cease to live.
Who said that? Mark Twain.
Wise man.
You are going to be fine tonight.
All right.
Now...
...showtime.
Gentlemen. Welcome.
We have a new girl for you tonight.
Something extra special.
It is a work-in-progress...
...so I apologize in advance
for the raw nature of the performance.
I will say, however...
...that is part of the charm.
It is my pleasure to introduce to you...
...this little baby doll.
Okay. This is how it's gonna go.
Amber will keep the bird on station.
Blondie, you'll operate the 50 cal here
and the 30 down there.
The rest of you, drop into the courtyard
and kill the creatures in your way.
Now, when you reach the nest,
you'll find the baby.
You'll have to slit its throat.
Down inside its neck are two crystals...
...that, when struck together, produce
the most magnificent fire you'll ever see.
Amber...
...put us on approach.
Roger that. Starting my run.
Nice.
Remember:
Don't ever write a check with your mouth
you can't cash with your ass.
Oh, yeah, and one more thing.
Don't wake the mother.
Here we go, ladies.
Go! Go! Go!
Go!
Up!
Whoa!
I got an idea.
Hold on!
I got you now!
Take that, you ugly mother.
Amber, where is she?
Check our 6. I don't see her.
Blondie, keep your eyes peeled.
I'll kill yo...
She's all yours, Baby.
I can't believe I did it.
Damn, that girl can dance.
See what you can do?
Wow, Amber.
Check it out.
- Halfway home.
- Yeah.
Let me see it.
- Oh.
You kiss the neck, it works every time.
- Good job.
- How'd we do?
Nice. Here.
And he didn't even notice.
No. No idea.
Good work, Amber.
- Thanks, Baby.
Cheers.
Cheers?
What are we celebrating?
Huh?
Who should I be congratulating?
It was just Babydoll's first time
on stage.
You know how scary that can be.
Yeah.
The bond of the theater.
Hm?
I mean, what else could it be?
I mean, it's not like any of you
have anything to hide, is it?
No.
It's not like anyone was in my office...
...messing with my shit.
No. It's not like people
are missing things.
You know, small little objects
here and there.
No. No, that would be outrageous.
That would be crazy.
Right?
Because we have such an obvious
explanation for this exuberance.
It's the fraternity of performers.
It's the adrenaline from
the curtain rising.
Maybe this is my fault.
You know, maybe I've just become
too familiar with you girls.
Maybe I need to make an example
of someone.
Re-establish the parameters
of our relationship. What do you think?
Blondie, girls?
And what about you?
Huh?
Oh.
You think you're special, don't you?
Well, I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
If I was not about to make a small fortune
on you with the High Roller...
...I would take you right now
and I would pop that little smile...
...right off of your face.
It saddens me that I have to
resort to threats with you girls.
I thought we were past that.
I just... I need this bullshit to stop!
Out of mutual respect.
Let's get things back to how they were.
Well...
So much for that little experiment.
What are you saying?
I'm saying it's over.
Right, Baby?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
Blue's onto us.
We had a deal.
If I say it's over, it's over.
We're this close, though.
We can't just stop.
Did you not hear Blue?
He knows we're up to something.
He knows what we're doing.
If he catches us for real,
it won't be a lecture. You saw him.
Sweet Pea. Rocket is right.
The High Roller comes tomorrow.
- Lf we can just stick with the plan till then...
- No! You're screwed.
We're out.
Rocket...
...we're out.
I'm finishing this.
We are all finishing this.
You know it's the only way
we can get out of here.
You're gonna choose her...
...someone you barely know...
...over me?
After all I've sacrificed for you.
I'm sorry.
Blondie?
What are you doing down there?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry, it's nothing.
What? What's wrong?
Did someone hurt you?
- No, it's not like that. It's really nothing.
- Clearly...
...it is not nothing.
Hey.
You can tell me. I am good listener.
Madame Gorski...
...please.
I know that look.
You think you're all alone,
and that no one can help you.
There is a way to fix anything.
Now...
...tell me what is wrong, child.
Okay.
Promise you can keep a secret?
- Yes.
Yes.
- Where the hell is she?
- I don't know.
We need your music.
You know what, forget it.
No, it's too late. Sweet Pea was right.
What are you talking about?
The three of us, we can...
I don't think we can do this.
I don't wanna do something stupid
that's gonna put you guys in danger.
I'm sorry.
Hey, we got this far, right?
I mean, that's something
not a lot of people could have done.
How bad can the High Roller be,
anyway?
Don't you girls have some work
you should be doing?
- You came to help us.
- No.
I came to keep you
from getting killed.
Thank you.
We don't have a lot of time.
If you're done with the pleasantries,
you got a dance to do.
Amber, radio.
What the hell are you doing?
You're gonna wanna watch this.
Turn off your mind
Relax and float downstream
It is not dying
Lay down all thought
Surrender to the void
It is shining
Ladies, this is what's on
our dance card for tonight.
The bomb, code-named "Kitchen Knife,"
is on a hijacked train.
It is protected by a couple dozen
mechanized gunmen.
The idea is simple:
Take care of the gunmen,
deactivate the bomb, then steal it.
The code numbers for the bomb and the
jetpacks for your escape are in that duffel.
Got it.
Sweet Pea.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
Well, there you have it.
You know, for those who fight for it...
...life has a flavor the sheltered
will never know.
Oh, yeah. One last thing.
The bomb's timer is set to detonate
when it reaches the city.
So if I were you, I'd hurry!
Weapons hot, ladies.
Hot.
- Hot.
I've got a lock.
Good luck.
- We're down.
Copy that.
Weapon will activate in four minutes,
15 seconds.
Codes!
Weapon will activate
in four minutes, 10 seconds.
in four minutes, five seconds.
A deactivation procedure
has been initiated.
Deactivation procedure complete.
Weapon deactivated.
Whoa!
Hurry, Amber.
We gotta get this thing out of here.
On my way.
Please refer to the operations manual.
For details on...
Amber, she's good.
I'm taking her out.
Guys, it's caught on something.
Hold up. We missed one.
Override procedures complete.
Weapon active.
Proximity warning.
Amber, the bomb's active.
Weapon will activate in 45 seconds.
Get free.
Whoa!
Weapon will activate in 25 seconds.
It's broke. It's not gonna work.
I'm on full burn. We'll go together.
It's not gonna carry the both of us.
- We have to try.
- Okay, we'll try.
But you've gotta promise me two things.
Rocket, let's go.
- The first thing is...
- Weapon will activate in 15 seconds.
...don't get mad about this.
About what?
This.
Rocket!
Weapon will activate in 10, nine...
...eight, seven, six...
...five, four...
...three, two, one.
The second thing is...
...when you get home...
...when you get free...
...you tell Mom I love her.
- I'll tell her.
- Mom.
I promise.
Oh, my.
You, what did you do?
You simple, inbred idiot.
Sir, don't know what happened. I just...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Get her up. Get her up, CJ!
Yes. Yeah, look.
I want you to look at what you did.
Look at what you did, you bitch!
Amber, sweetheart.
You've got Sweet Pea's slot
in tonight's show. Go get ready.
Go get ready.
Go!
Take her to the closet.
As for you...
...it's showtime.
The High Roller is here.
I need you to focus for me.
Ah. Thank you.
Girls?
Can you just gather around for a second?
I wanna say a few words.
That's all right.
You can just finish getting her dressed.
Okay. There we go.
Very nice.
All right.
I try to give you all...
...a good life.
I try. I do.
And all I ask for in return is just for...
...respect...
...honesty.
You know... Oh, that's okay, Margaret.
A give-and-take relationship.
But it's come to my attention...
It's come to our attention...
...that a few bad eggs...
...led by one little egg in particular...
...have spit in the face
of that generosity...
...and are plotting against me.
Me.
Your father.
Your lover.
Your employer.
Plotting to take from me
my most precious possessions.
Your very selves.
Blue, what you doing?
- Hm?
- You got the information. You have won.
This little fantasy of freedom
is all they have.
No, no, no. No one's buying that,
honey. No one's buying that, Vera.
There is nothing you can do to me
that you haven't already done.
- Unh.
- You listen to me, you old whore.
It's too late to play the good guy.
It's far too late.
You're suddenly not aware
of what it is we do here?
I teach them to survive you.
- All right.
- I'm sorry! I didn't mean to say anything.
I'm sorry.
No, Blondie.
I didn't mean to.
He said everything would be okay.
Blue, this is a mistake.
Please don't do this, okay?
That's right.
Our dear Blondie came to us...
...desperately trying to help her sisters
off this most dangerous path.
At first, we didn't even believe her.
But after hearing who was involved,
frankly, it started to make sense.
- Right here?
Blue.
Uh-huh. "Map. Fire. "
Looks like that chicken was counted
a little before it hatched.
Ain't that right, Amber?
You have anything to say? Anything?
Blue, we didn't... We were still...
You know what, sweetheart?
It's okay.
No!
- Oh, my God!
Okay, calm down.
This will all be over soon
and we can get back to business as usual.
Blondie, I wanna thank you
for everything you've done.
I am so sorry.
The thing is, we hate snitches, so...
No!
Okay. Here.
I hate guns.
I hope everyone's learned
a valuable lesson here.
Especially you, Madame Gorski.
Get her out of here.
Let's get these bodies out of here, please.
And the rest of you, you got a show to do.
So go on, go get them, girls.
Make it count.
I've been thinking a lot...
...about all that money
you're gonna make me.
I've been thinking a lot about the
High Roller and his hands all over you.
I've been thinking about
all those people out there...
...just watching you
and lusting after you.
And you'd think that would
give me pleasure.
I mean, I'm in the business of pleasure.
But you know what
it makes me feel like?
I'm gonna be honest with you.
It makes me feel like I'm this little boy...
...sitting in the corner of the sandbox...
...while everybody
gets to play with my toys...
...but me.
So you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna take my toys
and I'm gonna go home.
I'm going home now...
Oh, that's good! That's it.
Oh, is that it?!
That's my little bitch.
This what you like?
Come here!
What? No, no, no.
Come on. Come on!
Did you lose your fight? Huh?
No.
I just found it.
You'll never have me.
Ever.
- Sweet Pea.
- Where's Amber and Blondie?
It's just us now.
We have to go, Sweet Pea. Come on.
- That's it.
- Okay.
- Now what?
- Wait for it.
Come on.
Damn it.
This can't be.
We did everything right.
A map, fire, a knife, a key,
and one thing more.
One thing more.
It's me.
What?
Oh, it's me. Of course it's me.
It's the only way
this ever could have ended.
What do you mean?
I'm saying you go home.
Go home to your family.
You tell your mom what Rocket said.
Make her happy.
Go out and live a normal life...
...love...
...be free.
You have to live for all of us now.
- Baby, no. You can't do that.
- Yes, Sweet Pea.
You're the strongest.
You're the only one of us
that ever had a chance out there.
You going home and living,
that's how we win.
It's okay. It's okay. It's better this way.
Now listen.
I'm gonna walk out there...
...and when they come after me,
you go, okay?
There's gotta be another way.
No.
This is right.
This was never my story.
It's yours.
Now, don't screw it up, okay?
You stay off the roads
and you find a bus station, all right?
You're gonna be fine.
Where you going, sweetheart?
I said, where you going?
There you are.
You gave us quite a scare, you know?
Where am I?
You're safe for now.
I don't know how to put this delicately so
I will spare you the insult of being vague...
...that you and I are supposed
to screw.
I hope you'll forgive my language...
...but I think you'll find it is in keeping
with the spirit of the arrangement.
Now I have absolutely no intention
of simply taking you.
In fact...
...I can think of nothing more offensive.
You see, I am what you might call
a man who has everything.
And yet, I lack the one thing
money can't buy.
- Love?
- Close.
Truth...
...is more accurate.
I seek a true moment,
a moment of truth.
In this...
...world of lies.
It just so happens that...
...that moment...
...that fragile, delicate thing
like a glass egg...
...or a sand castle,
well, that moment...
...can only be given
by a non-faker.
A non-actor.
That's you.
I don't understand.
Well, I have spent...
...a small fortune
getting you in this room.
This golden cage.
You're supposed to give yourself to me.
It's completely physical.
I might have your body...
...but the real you that...
...intangible, and indefinable spark
that is you.
Well, that you I will never know.
And, yet, that is precisely what I want.
I'm sorry.
You seem really nice.
You want me to lie to you?
No, I don't.
All I require from you...
...is a sliver of a moment.
To have you not by force...
...but simply as a man and a woman.
To see in your eyes
that simple truth...
...that you give yourself to me freely.
Not because you have to...
...but because you want to.
Now, of course, you're such a gem...
...I will give as well.
I'm willing to give you freedom.
Pure and total freedom.
Freedom from the drudgery
of every day life...
...freedom as abstract ideal.
Freedom from pain...
...freedom from responsibility...
...freedom from guilt...
...from regret...
...freedom from sadness...
...freedom from loss...
...the freedom to be happy.
Don't close your eyes.
I need you to look at me.
The freedom to love.
Jesus.
Did...?
Did you see the way she looked at me?
Just in that last moment. It was like...
Doctor?
Is it done?
Dr. Gorski, what do you know
about this one?
Uh, there was something very peculiar.
Yes. Her mother's death plunged her
into a deep depression.
And then in a fit,
she accidentally killed her sister.
Poor child.
It's a shame I couldn't do more for her.
I wasn't given much time, you see.
Yes, but you recommended
the procedure.
Oh, I'm afraid not.
I will admit she has been
quite a handful.
In just one week here,
she stabbed an orderly, started a fire...
...and helped another patient to escape.
But I don't agree with this solution,
doctor.
But why would you sign for a procedure
you don't agree with?
Well, I...
That is your signature, is it not?
I've been doing this
for quite some time, doctor...
...and to be honest with you, I've wondered
myself whether or not it's right.
And I have seen some tortured souls
in here. Believe me.
But this one...
Something in her eyes.
I've never seen anyone that...
It's the way she looked at me.
It's like she wanted me to do it.
I hope it helps her.
Hi.
You remember me?
Listen. Listen, I got a bad feeling, okay?
These boys do too.
This is not the way
we should be running this place.
We don't run the place. I run it.
In the chair.
Look...
...I'm not...
- I'm not hurting these girls anymore.
- I'm not doing this.
Guys, don't do this to me now, please.
I need her in that chair.
Put her in the goddamn chair!
Thank you.
Close the door, please.
What? What is it, you're not here? Huh?
You're not here, you're in paradise?
No, no, no. No, no, no.
No, no, no.
You're still here.
You're here with me.
In all this shit.
And you don't go away unless I say so.
Okay?
That's not right.
Come back.
No! No!
I said you don't go!
You come back to me.
- Stop right there. Move away from the girl.
What are you doing?
Aah! Wait. Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. Aah!
What in God's name
have you been doing up here?
I wasn't doing anything. Look at her.
She's gone. Look at her face!
She's not here.
What do you think I wanna do?
I take care of these girls.
I look out for them.
These are my girls. Tell them.
Tell them!
Get him out of here.
- Now.
- Aah! Wait. Wait, wait, wait! Wait.
It's not me you want, it's her stepfather.
I'll tell you everything. I'll tell you...
I'll tell you about the money.
Just keep going down the hall.
You all right, miss?
Miss?
The mystery of whose story it will be...
...of who draws the curtain.
Who is it that chooses our steps
in the dance?
Who drives us mad...
...lashes us with whips...
...and crowns us with victory
when we survive the impossible?
Who is it...
...that does all these things?
Bus 22 southbound
to Fort Wayne will now begin loading.
Please have your tickets ready
to show the driver.
Excuse me, miss?
Miss, can we have a word?
Is there a problem, gentlemen?
This doesn't concern you.
I have questions for the lady.
Well, could you make it snappy?
I need to stay on schedule.
- We understand.
- Do you?
That young woman's been on this bus
since Hartford.
I don't see what she could possibly know
about anything happening around here.
Is that true, miss?
I just let her off to use the restroom.
Mine's not working.
- All right.
Oh, and one more thing.
- She's been a joy the entire journey.
- Yes, I said, all right.
Sorry about the inconvenience, miss.
You have yourself a nice trip now.
It's no problem.
- I don't have a ticket.
- I know. It's okay.
Go find a seat in the back.
Try and get some sleep.
We got a long way to go.
Thank you.
Who honors those we love
with the very life we live?
Who sends monsters to kill us...
...and at the same time
sings that we'll never die?
Who teaches us what's real
and how to laugh at lies?
Who decides why we live
and what we'll die to defend?
Who chains us?
And who holds the key
that can set us free?
It's you.
You have all the weapons you need.
Now fight.
SUBTITLES BY : manishpk2007